Henry Allen Moe Papers 1920-1975 Mss.B.M722
American Philosophical Society
- Henry Allen Moe Papers, 1920-1975; 120 lin. feet (Box 1-344)
  - Flexner, James Thomas
  - Flexner, Simon
  - Flick, Hugh M
  - Flom, Floyd O
  - Flores, Alejandro
  - Florey, Harold
  - Florey, Sir Howard W
  - Florey, Lady Margaret
  - Florida Atlantic University
  - Flory, W S
  - Flygt, Sten Gunnar
  - Flynn, Edward F
  - Foldats, E
  - Foley, Charles
  - Foley, Leon F
  - Folger Library
  - Folsom, R G
  - Fong, Wen
  - Fontaine, George J
  - Fooshee, Malcolm
  - Foote, Mrs. Miriam
  - Foote, Paul D
  - Ford, Edwin D
  - Ford, Edwin D, Jr.
  - Ford, Ford Maddox
  - Ford, George B
  - Ford, Guy Stanton
  - Ford, J D M
  - Ford Foundation
  - Forman, George V D
  - Forman, John Van Doren
  - Forman, Mildred
  - Fort Wadsworth Committee for a Living National Park Memorial
  - Fortuna, Brian J
  - Fosdick, Raymond B
  - Fosdick, Mrs. Raymond B
  - Foster, A W
  - Foster, D B
  - Foundation Center
  - Foundation for the Community of Artists
  - Foundations - Officers
  - Fountaine, George J
  - Fowler, Burton P
  - Fowler, Manet
  - Fox, Hugh
  - Fox, Irwin Sonny
  - Foyles Book Shop
  - Fraley, Pierre C
  - Francis, Sir Frank
  - François & Cie
  - Frankel, Jesse J
  - Frankel, Sandor
  - Frankfurter, Felix
  - Franklin, Benjamin, Papers of
  - Franklin, Carl M
  - Franklin Institute
  - Fraser, Joseph T, Jr.
  - Frazee, Mrs. Elizabeth
  - Fred, E B
  - Frederick, John T
  - Freehafer, Edward
  - Freeman, Douglas Southall
  - Freeman, Gaylord A
  - Freeman, Lucy
  - Freeman, Orville
  - French, George F
  - French, Paul Comly
  - Freund, Gerald
  - Frey, Katherine
  - Freyre, Gilberto
  - Fribourg and Treyer, Tobacconists
  - Frick Art Reference Library
  - Fridley, Russell W
  - Fried, Michael
  - Friedman, Karl R
  - Friedman, Martin
  - Friedmann, Herbert
  - Friend, Albert C
  - Friendly, Fred W
  - Friends Council on Education
  - Friener, Paul
  - Froelicher, Charles
  - Frost, James A
  - Frothingham, Elizabeth
  - Fruhman, Martin
  - Fruton, Joseph S
  - Fry, Edward
  - Fry, Varian
  - Frye, Roland
  - Fuess, Claude
  - Fuller, Lillian Gebhard
  - Fuller, Walter D
  - Fulton, Joe
  - Fulton, John F
  - Fulton, Mrs. John
  - Fund Raising Law
  - Fuoss, Robert
  - Furbay, John Harvey
  - Furst, Clyde
  - Future Plans
  - Gabetti, Gianluigi
  - Gabriel, Ralph H
  - Gaebelein, Donn M
  - Gainey, Daniel C
  - Gainey, Daniel James
  - Galantière, Lewis
  - Gala´vn, Guerrero
  - Galpin, Perrin C
  - Gamble, Sidney D
  - Gammage, Grady
  - Gammell, R H Ives
  - Gannett, Lewis
  - Gans, Carl
  - Ganter, Carl
  - Garcia, Carlos Bosch
  - Gardner, Edward H
  - Gardner, James
  - Gardner, John W
  - Gardner, Le Roy
  - Gardner, Steven
  - Garfield, Eugene
  - Garnett, William
  - Garnsey, Morris E
  - Garrison, Joshua
  - Garrison, Joshua, Jr.
  - Garside, Charles
  - Garside, Mrs. Charles
  - Garvin, C C
  - Gash, Frederick
  - Gasslander, Mrs. Alma
  - Gassner, John
  - Gavan, W S
  - Gavert, Mrs. Paul
  - Gavit, John Palmer
  - Geesa, Martha G
  - Geffen, Felicia
  - Gemina Olive Oil Company
  - Genauer, Emily
  - General Bronze Corporation
  - General Electric Company
  - General Motors Institute
  - Genn, Sally
  - George, L A, II
  - George, Lincoln
  - George Westinghouse Centennial Forum
  - Georgetown University
  - Gerald, J Edward
  - Gettell, Richard Glenn
  - Ghali, Mirrit
  - Gibson, Ann Judith... bibliography of Alfred L. Kroeber
  - Gibson, Margaret
  - Gibson, Mercedes
  - Giddens, Paul H
  - Giddings, Herman B
  - Giddings, Will
  - Gifford, Walter S
  - Gihosh, T
  - Gil, Harry
  - Gilbertson, Edna
  - Gilchrist, Huntington
  - Gilder, Rodman
  - Gilder, Rosamond
  - Gilgamesh
  - Gill, Brendan
  - Gill, O A
  - Gillam, V A
  - Gillespie, Charles C
  - Gillies, Donald A
  - Gillin, John
  - Gillman, Francis
  - Gilmor, Frances
  - Gilmore, Myron P
  - Gilmore, Robert W
  - Gilpatric, Chadbourne
  - Gilpatric, Roswell
  - Gimbel, Mrs. Bernard F
  - Gimbel, Mrs.Louis S, Jr.
  - Ginastera, Mercedes and Alberto
  - Ginsburg, Michael
  - Gipson, Lawrence Henry
  - Girden, Edward
  - Givens, Meredith B
  - Glaccum, John H
  - Glassgold, Adolph Cook
  - Gleason, Harold
  - Glickman, Mrs. Florence Lewison
  - Gloster, Monica, and Martin
  - Gnauer, Emily
  - Gnoli, Raniero
  - Godfrey, Hollis
  - Godron, Mrs. Harry
  - Godwin, Blake-More
  - Goetsch, J B
  - Gold, Albert
  - Goldberg, Maxwell H
  - Goldblatt, Harry
  - Golden, Charles
  - Goldman, Eric F
  - Goldman, Richard Franko
  - Gomes, Alair O
  - Gomes, Alercio M
  - Gomez, Domingo
  - Gonzalez, N V M
  - Gonzalez, Poublé
  - Gonzalez, Xavier
  - Gonzalez-Robles, Luis
  - Gooch, R K
  - Goodall, Donald
  - Goodard, Henry W
  - Goodchild, Donald
  - Goode, Frederick W
  - Goodhart, Arthur L
  - Goodrich, Hunter
  - Goodrich, Lloyd Carrington
  - Goodspeed, Thomas H
  - Goodwin, Philip L
  - Goodwin, Richard N
  - Goodwin, T Campbell
  - Gordon, Alasdair C
  - Gordon, Albert H
  - Gordon, Milton M
  - Gordon, Phyllis Goodhart (Mrs. John D.)
  - Gorelik, Mordecai
  - Gorham, Evelyn M
  - Goribar, Joaquin Cortina
  - Gosnell, C F
  - Goudvis, Albert Charles
  - Goudvis, Helen
  - Gough, H B
  - Gould, Laurence M
  - Gould, Peter
  - Gould, Samuel Brookner
  - Goupil, Vibert & Co.
  - Gove, George
  - Gow, J Steele
  - Goytia de Allende, Maria Angelice
  - Grace, Virginia R
  - Grafflin, Allan
  - Graham, Eleanor
  - Graham, Howard J
  - Graham, Jack W
  - Graham, Martha
  - Gramm, Hanns
  - Grand Central Station - Lost and Found Dept.
  - Granrud, John
  - Grant, A D
  - Grant, Kenneth
  - Grant, Pryor
  - Grantees' vouchers
  - Gravem, Axel B
  - Graves, Mortimer
  - Graveson, R H
  - Gravett, P W
  - Gray, James
  - Grayson, Ferdinand V
  - Green, Charles
  - Green, Earl L
  - Griswold, Erwin
  - Gronstvedt, Erik Jahr
  - Grosse, Mrs. Doris
  - Grossman, Bernard A
  - Group for Contemporary Music
  - Grubsten, Eugene
  - Gruenenfelder, Lois
  - Grummon, Stuart E
  - Guaranty Trust Company
  - Guarnieri, Camargo
  - Gueron, Georges
  - Guggenheim, Harry Frank
  - Guggenheim, Harry Frank, Foundation
  - Guggenheim, Harry Frank, Foundation
    - Abernathy
    - Adams, John C
    - American Association for the Advancement of Science
    - Annual Meeting
    - Ardrey, Robert
    - Articles
    - Anzar, Ramón
    - Bassett, Perston R
    - Beck, Robert A
    - Behavioral Sciences Foundation
    - Biological psychiatry
    - Blurton-Jones
    - Bogard, Travis
    - Brown, R. Manning, Jr.
    - Callagy, John M
    - Canadian Peace Research
    - Carmichael, Leonard
    - Central Afar
    - Chagnon, Napoleon
    - Chandler, Dorothy
    - Chisholm, James Stewart
    - Conference: International Decision Making
    - Daniel Island Property
    - De Vore, Irven
    - Dilworth, J R
    - Dominance Behavior
    - Doolittle, J H
    - Estate appraisal: books
    - Emerson, Thomas I
    - Erim, Kenan T
    - Fellowship program
    - Film: Promised Lands
    - Financial report
    - Fitts, Mary
    - Fitts, Paul M
    - Fitzmaurice-Martin
    - Flagg, William H
    - Flores, Carlos Guzmán
    - Gallegos-Cigarroa, Alfredo
    - Garcia-Castells, Esther
    - Goodall-Hamburg Proposal
    - Gottlieb, Leo
    - Griffin, John A
    - Gross, Mason W
    - Hanes, John W
    - Herd, G Ronald
    - Howell, F Clark
    - Human Ethnology Workshop
    - Ingersoll, R Sturgis
    - Johansen, D C
    - Kling, Arthur
    - Koch, Edward I
    - Larsen, Roger R
    - Lawson-Johnston, Peter
    - Leakey, Louis S B
    - Leakey Foundation
    - Lefkowitz, Louis J
    - Lifton, Robert Jay
    - Lindbergh, Charles A
    - McClellan, Bruce
    - Man's Relation to Man
    - Man's Relation to Man - Dominance
    - Man's Relation to Man Project
    - Marshack, Alexander
    - Martin, Malachi
    - Maxey, E Stanton
    - Minutes of Fellowship Committee
    - Moe-Fountaine
    - Newcomb, Theodore
    - Nolte, Richard
    - Owen, Michael
    - Parker, John E
    - Pendray, G Edward
    - Ph.D....Dramatic Art...Berkeley, California
    - Pickslay, F Frith
    - Pincus, William
    - Program proposed by Fox and Tiger [see also Tiger and Fox]
    - Proposals for grants
    - Raser, John R
    - Reports, articles
    - Resume of papers
    - Ripley, S Dillon
    - Rogers, Carroll, Jr.
    - Rubinstein, Jonathan B
    - Ryan, Christine
    - Schizophrenic behavior
    - Schwartz reports
    - Schwartz, David C
    - Sharp, Gene
    - Shaw, Joseph
    - Shiloh, Ailon
    - Simmons, R W
    - Somit, Albert
    - Steen, M C
    - Steinbeck, John
    - Straus, Roger, Jr.
    - Symons, Donald
    - Symposium on dominance
    - Thompson, William M
    - Thomson, Meldrim, Jr.
    - Tiger and Fox, proposed projects
    - Tribe that hides from Man
    - Triver, R
    - Tuersky and Kahneman
    - Wilson, Carroll
  - Guggenheim, John Simon, Memorial Foundation
    - Committee of Fellows
    - Communications with Secretaries
    - Docket
    - Fellows
    - General Correspondence
    - IRS
    - Leighton Digest Book
    - Memorandum for Trustees on Future Plans
    - Minutes
    - Notice to applicants
    - Report
    - Retirement Annuity Plan
    - Retirement letters
    - Retirement of Henry Allen Moe
    - Staff
    - Wilson, Carroll
    - Unamerican Accusations
  - Guggenheim, Olga H
  - Guggenheim, Peter
  - Guggenheim, Solomon R., Foundation
    - Audit Report
    - Director's Report
    - Minutes
    - Museum
    - Museum Director's report
    - Museum Dubuffet, Jean: a retrospective
  - Gugler, Eric
  - Guldbeck, Per
  - Gundahl, Trygve
  - Gundshaw, Kathleen
  - Gunn, Vigel C
  - Gunsalus, I C
  - Gutterman, Leon
  - Guy, W G
  - Guzman, Antonio J Lemos
  - Guzmán, Leonardo
  - Gwyn, Julian
  - Gwynn, Charles B
  - Haberly, Lloyd
  - Hackett, E F
  - Hackett, Frank S
  - Hackett, Lewis W
  - Hackney, J M
  - Hagenah, Mrs. John J
  - Haggerty, Richard
  - Haight, Mrs. Anne
  - Haight, Sherman
  - Haight, Sidney
  - Haiti
  - Hale, Beverly
  - Hale, Richard W
  - Hale, William Harlan
  - Halifax, Lady Dorothy
  - Hall, Lois
  - Hall, Sir Noel
  - Hall, Robert King
  - Halle, Kay
  - Halle, Louis
  - Halliday, F R
  - Hallie, Philip
  - Hallock, Gerard
  - Hallowell, Burton C
  - Halperin, Gregorio
  - Halpern, J
  - Halverson, Marvin P
  - Hamburg, David A, and Jane van Lawick-Goodall
  - Hamburger, Max
  - Hamer, Philip M
  - Hamilton, Alexander
  - Hamilton, Alexander, Papers of
  - Hamilton, Earl J
  - Hamilton, Leila
  - Hamilton, Portia
  - Hamilton, W Paul
  - Hamlin, Lewis P
  - Hamline University
  - Hammett, Frederick S
  - Hammond, Bray
  - Hammond, Gordon J. Analytical study of the socio-economic status of teachers...
  - Hammond, Mrs. John Henry
  - Hanbury, H G
  - Hancher, Virgil M
  - Hand, Learned
  - Hand, Wayland D
  - Handler, Milton
  - Handlin, Oscar
  - Handman, Wynn
  - Hanger, Harriet
  - Hanke, Lewis U
  - Hanks, Nancy
  - Hanna, Paul R
  - Hanna, William
  - Hansen, Erling W
  - Hansen,and Sons
  - Hanson, Elliott S
  - Hanson, Howard
  - Harbeson, John F
  - Harcourt, Mrs. Simon
  - Hard, Frederick
  - Harding
  - Hardy, Claude
  - Hardy, Le Grand
  - Haring, Clarence H
  - Harlow, A Brooks
  - Harlow, V T
  - Harnwell, Gaylord P
  - Harper, Francis
  - Harrar, J George
  - Harriman, Averell
  - Harrington, Catherine M
  - Harrington, Lucille
  - Harris, George
  - Harris, Lynn H
  - Harris, T George
  - Harrison, L P
  - Harrison, Wallace Kirkman
  - Harrold, Frank
  - Harron, Robert
  - Hart, Derek O
  - Hart, Mrs. H H
  - Hart, Robert G
  - Hartig, Albert
  - Hartle, Henry W
  - Hartman, Carl G
  - Hartman, Joyce
  - Hartman, Justin J
  - Hartt, Frederick
  - Hartwell, Mrs. Martha Winston
  - Hartwick College
  - Hartzell, Karl D
  - Harvard University
  - Harvard University Press
  - Harvard University Society of Fellows
  - Harvey, Anthony
  - Harvey, Mrs. C P
  - Harvey, Cyril P
  - Harvey, Jean
  - Haskell, Henry S
  - Haskins, Caryl Parker
  - Haskins, George L
  - Haskins, John F
  - Hass, Robert Donald
  - Hastings, Albert Baird
  - Hastings, John
  - Hastings, William T
  - Hatch, J D
  - Hatcher, Harlan
  - Hathaway, Mrs. Christine D
  - Haubiel, Charles
  - Haury, Emil W
  - Haustetter, A
  - Havegen, Einar
  - Hawkes, Anna L Rose
  - Hawkes, H E
  - Hawkes, John
  - Hawkins, Eliot D
  - Hawkins, Frances
  - Haworth, Leland J
  - Hay, Clarence L
  - Hay, Harold R
  - Hayden, Joel B
  - Hayden, J Willard
  - Hayden, William M
  - Haydn, Hiran
  - Hayes, Bartlett
  - Hayes, Carlton J H
  - Hayes, Mrs. Clare
  - Hayes, Francis
  - Hayes, Harold
  - Hayes, Helen
  - Hayes, Herbert K
  - Haynie, Hugh
  - Hayward, John F
  - Hayzus, Jorge Roberto
  - Hazard, James
  - Hazard, John N
  - Hazard, Patrick D
  - Heald, Henry T
  - Healey, John F, Jr.
  - Healey, Mrs. Mabel
  - Healey, William Vincent
  - Heard, Alexander
  - Hearn Foundation
  - Hebrew Union College
  - Heckman, A A
  - Heckscher, August
  - Heckscher, Claude
  - Hectographed certificates of vouchers
  - Hectographed reports of grantees to Coordinator
  - Hedberg, Hollis D
  - Hedden, Stuart
  - Hedgeman, Anna Arnold
  - Heermance, Radcliffe
  - Heffner, Hubert C
  - Heidelberger, Michael
  - Heimoz, Michael R
  - Heindell, Richard Heathcote
  - Heise, Doris
  - Heiser, Victor George
  - Heiskell, Andrew
  - Heister, Elsa R
  - Hell, Mrs. Thomas
  - Heller, G H
  - Hellman, Geoffrey T
  - Hellmann, Eva
  - Helsabeck, Fred
  - Hemenway, Robert
  - Hendel, Charles W
  - Henderson, A D
  - Henderson, Gregory
  - Henderson, L J
  - Henderson, M
  - Henderson, Martha T
  - Hendrickson, G L
  - Hendrix, W S
  - Henle, James
  - Hennessy, Paul Kirby
  - Henniker-Gotley, G Rainald
  - Henry, Barklie McKee
  - Henry, Jules
  - Henry Holt and Company
  - Henry Street Settlement
  - Henson, A E
  - Hermann, William
  - Hernan, Gustave O
  - Hernandez, Julio
  - Hernandez de Alba, Gregorio
  - Herpers, Richard
  - Herrick, Amy
  - Herrick, C Judson
  - Herrick Company
  - Herrick, Samuel
  - Herring, Hubert
  - Herron, Francis
  - Hersey, John
  - Hersey, Rex
  - Hertie, Marshall
  - Hertzberg, Sidney
  - Herz, Joseph J
  - Herzog, Fritz
  - Heschel, Rabbi Abraham J
  - Heslin, James, Jr.
  - Hess, Mrs. Gertrude D
  - Hess, J William
  - Hesselman, Leo W
  - Hester, James M
  - Hetzel, Ralph
  - Hewitt, Barnard
  - Hewitt, John Vance
  - Hewitt, R T
  - Hexter, George
  - Hexter, J H
  - Heydenryk, Henry, Jr.
  - Hicks, John D
  - High School of Music and Art
  - High School Teachers
  - Hightower, John B
  - Hilberry, Norman
  - Hilgard, Ernest R
  - Hill, A V
  - Hill, Adelaide Cromwell
  - Hill, Listerq
  - Hill School
  - Hiller, A D
  - Hilley, Howard S
  - Hillis, Margaret
  - Hiltunen, Mrs. Eila
  - Himsworth, Harold P
  - Hinchman, Margaretta S
  - Hinderaker, Ivan
  - Hinshelwood, Cyril
  - Hirsch, Joseph
  - Hirschman, Albert O
  - Hirschorn, Elisa
  - Hitchcock, Alfred
  - Hobler, Anne S
  - Hochschild, Harold K
  - Hocutt, John E
  - Hodges, John C
  - Hodgkinson, Mrs. Laura Cabot
  - Hodgson, William
  - Hoecker, Gustavo
  - Hoffman, Paul
  - Hofstra University
  - Hoggins, Charles
  - Hohenberg, John
  - Holden, Donald
  - Holdridge, L R
  - Holdsworth, William S
  - Hollaender, Alexander
  - Holland, Kenneth
  - Holland, Leicester
  - Holleman, John L
  - Holleman, Wilbur
  - Hollister, John B
  - Holm, Therese C
  - Holman, Frank E
  - Holman, William M
  - Holmberg, Allan A
  - Holmes, Eugene C
  - Holmes, George
  - Holmes, Grace Branley
  - Holmes, H A
  - Holmes, Mrs. Lowell L
  - Holmes, Malcolm
  - Holroyd, Mrs. Freda
  - Holroyd, Michael
  - Holton, Gerald
  - Hood, Irene R
  - Hopi Cultural Center
  - Hopkins, Jeannette
  - Hopkins, Vivian C
  - Hopkinson, Charles
  - Hoppin, Mrs. Catherine
  - Hoppin, Frederick S
  - Horan, Anne
  - Horgan, Paul
  - Horn, Milton
  - Hornbeck, Stanley K
  - Hornbeck, Mrs. Vivienne
  - Hornig, Donald F
  - The Horse Ocean
  - Horty, Caryl Aimee
  - Hoskins, George L
  - Hospital Association of New York State
  - Hospital Audiences, Inc.
  - Hospital for Special Surgery
  - Hospital Week
  - Hotel Du Pont
  - Hotel Maria Luisa
  - Hotel Mayfair
  - Hotel New Weston
  - Hotel William Byrd
  - Houghton, Arthur A
  - Houghton, Norris
  - Houpert, Henry
  - Houssay, B A
  - Houston, Herbert
  - Howard, Mrs. Campbell
  - Howard, Leon
  - Howes, Edward L
  - Hoxie, G Gordon
  - Hoy, John C
  - Hubbard, Mrs. Barbara
  - Hubbell, D S
  - Hudgins, Edward W
  - Hudnet, William H
  - Hudson, Guild
  - Huggins, Charles B
  - Huggins, H D
  - Hughes, Charles H
  - Hughes, Glenn
  - Hull, Cordell
  - Hull, William
  - Humanities
  - Humber, Robert Lee
  - Hume, H Harold
  - Hume, Nelson
  - Hummel, Charles F
  - Hummell, Arthur E
  - Humphrey, Hubert
  - Humphrey, John P
  - Humphrey, Richard F
  - Humphrey, Willard D
  - Humphreys, A R
  - Hunnisett, F W
  - Hunsaker, Mrs. Alice P
  - Hunsaker, J C
  - Hunt, Dora G
  - Hunt, Everett
  - Hunter, Kremit
  - Hunter, Walter S
  - Hunter, T Willard
  - Hurst, Willard
  - Hurwitz, Mrs. Edith
  - Huseby, Mrs. Louise
  - Huser, Thomas E
  - Hussein, King
  - Husted, James W
  - Hutchins, Mrs. Carleen M
  - Hutchins, Robert S
  - Hutchins, Susan
  - Hutchinson, William B
  - Hutson, Mary Beth
  - Hyde, Mrs. Donald F
  - Hyde Hall
  - Hyman, Edgar C
  - Hypro Engineering, Inc.
  - Hyslop, Beatrice F
  - Ignacio-Pinto, Marc
  - Improving Foundation performance
  - Inclán y Costa, Clemente
  - India House, Inc.
  - Ingles, Frances
  - Ingraham, R K
  - Inman, Samuel Guy
  - Institute for Advanced Studies in the Theatre Arts
  - Institute for Advanced Study
  - Institute for the Future
  - Institute of Contemporary Art
  - Institute of Current World Affairs
  - Institute of Current World Affairs Reports
  - Institute of Inter-American Affairs
  - Institute of International Education
  - Institute of Modern Art
  - Institute on Ethics
  - Insurance - Bankers Life
  - Inter-American Artistic and Intellectual Relations
  - Inter-American House
  - Inter-American Institute of Fine Arts
  - Inter-American Statistical Institute
  - International Council for Philosophy and Humanistic Studies
  - International Council on the Future of the University
  - International Creative Center
  - International Educational Pictures, Inc.
  - International Foundation for Art Research
  - International Institute of Iberian Colonial Art
  - International Oceanographic Foundation
  - International Society for Contemporary Music
  - International Study Center
  - Investments by Private Foundations
  - Ireland, Bernard
  - Ireland, Richard M
  - Irving, Susan K
  - Irwin, Mary Alice
  - Isaacs, Norman E
  - Iselin, Lewis, Jr.
  - Iselin, Mrs. Sally
  - Islamic Culture, Committee for
  - Issawi, Charles
  - Italian Art and Landscape Foundation
  - Iushewitz, Morris
  - Ives, Herbert E
  - Ives, Mrs. Herbert E
  - Ives, Irving M
  - Ivins, William M, Jr.
  - Jack, Thomas J
  - Jackson, Elmer C
  - Jackson, Harry L
  - Jackson, W C
  - Jackson, W Turrentine
  - Jacob, Mrs. Devon M
  - Jacobs, Albert C
  - Jacobs, Wilbur
  - Jaffray, Norman
  - Jahrnack, Philip
  - James, Henry
  - James, P A
  - James, Preston
  - James, Sidney L
  - Jamieson, Ivan W, and Hazel Jamieson Kraemer
  - Jamieson, Mitchell
  - Janney, J Elliott
  - Jarnach, Philipp
  - Jastremski, Michael S
  - Javits, Jacob K
  - Jay, John
  - Jay, John C
  - Jay, John C, Jr.
  - Jay, Pierre
  - Jayne, Horace H F
  - Jeffery, R W
  - Jenkins, Elsa
  - Jenness, Diamond
  - Jennings, Charles E
  - Jepsen, Glenn L
  - Jerome Lecture Committee
  - Jerome Lectureship
  - Jessup, Philip C
  - Jessup, Walter C
  - Jewell, Edward Alden
  - Jiggitts, Louis M
  - Jiménez, Juan Ramón
  - Joel, Brother
  - Johansen, Charles
  - Johansen, Gunnar
  - Johansen, John C
  - Johns Hopkins University
  - Johnson, Alvin
  - Johnson, Charles S
  - Johnson, Charles W
  - Johnson, Evert A
  - Johnson, Geraldine
  - Johnson, Herbert F
  - Johnson, Joseph E
  - Johnson, Ludwell H, III
  - Johnson, Mrs. Lyndon B [Lady Bird]
  - Johnson, Mrs. Paul E
  - Johnson, Philip
  - Johnson, Pyke
  - Johnston, Robert L
  - Jones, Mrs. Agnes
  - Jones, Arthur W
  - Jones, Betsy
  - Jones, David
  - Jones, Fido (cat and dog correspondence)
  - Jones, Frances N
  - Jones, Howard Mumford
  - Jones, Howard P
  - Jones, Janis
  - Jones, Leslie
  - Jones, Louis
  - Jones, Mrs. Louis C
  - Jones, Mrs. Max Kastner [Vivian]
  - Jones, Molly Mason
  - Jones, Robert L
  - Jones, Thomas Jesse
  - Jones, Willis Knapp
  - Jones, William T
  - Jordan, Weymouth T
  - Jordan, Mrs. Weymouth T
  - Jordaõ, Vera Pacheco
  - Jorrin, Miguel
  - Josephus, Devereaux C
  - Judd, William H
  - Juhlin, Alton P
  - Junior Programs
  - Juta, Jan
  - Kabotie, Fred
  - Kaiden, F G
  - Kaiser Foundation Hospitals
  - Kamenoff, Arthur Q
  - Kamenoff, Mrs. Arthur Q
  - Kandel, I L
  - Kane, Albert E
  - Kane, R Keith
  - Kantorowicz, Ernst H
  - Kaplan, Sheldon Z
  - Karpel, Bernard
  - Karsten, Karl G
  - Kartzke, George
  - Kashke (?), Klaus
  - Katan, Clarence
  - Kates, George N
  - Katona, Paul
  - Katz, Mrs. David (Gene)
  - Katz, Elias
  - Kaufman, Edgar
  - Kazan, Elia
  - Kebbon, Eric
  - Keck, Mrs. Caroline
  - Keck, Sheldon
  - Keele, Harold M
  - Keele and Dempsey
  - Keeler, Clyde
  - Keene, Mrs. Helen
  - Keeney, Barnaby
  - Keeney, Elizabeth
  - Keir, Sir D Lindsay
  - Keiser, David M
  - Kelemen, Pál
  - Keller, Deane
  - Kelley, Nicholas
  - Kellogg, Frank B
  - Kellogg, I N
  - Kelly, Constance
  - Keltin, Louis B
  - Kendall, George M
  - Kendall, John P
  - Kendall, William L
  - Kendall, Willmeere
  - Kendrew, A E
  - Kendrick, A J
  - Kendrick, Mrs. Elva M
  - Kenison, Frank Rowe
  - Keniston, Hayward
  - Kenler, Hans
  - Kennan, George
  - Kennedy, E S
  - Kennedy, Gail
  - Kennedy, John F
  - Kennedy, Robert
  - Kennedy, Mrs. Robert
  - Kent, H W
  - Kepes, Gyorgy
  - Kephart, Samuel Robinson
  - Keppel, Charles T
  - Keppel, F P
  - Keppel, Francis
  - Keppel, Frederick P
  - Kerfoot, Margaret
  - Kerfoot, Paul
  - Kernochan, Marshall
  - Kerr, Clark
  - Kerr, Paul S
  - Kessler, Hans
  - Kettner, Robert L
  - Keyes, H M R
  - Kidd, Charles
  - Kidder, Mrs. Alfred V
  - Kidder Smith, G E
  - Kieffer, Paul
  - Kiermaier, J W
  - Kiger, Joseph C
  - Kilgen, A G
  - Kiger, Joseph C
  - Kilgour, Raymond L
  - Kilham, Walter H, Jr.
  - Kimball, Clarence M
  - Kimball, Lindsley F
  - Kimball, Richard
  - Kimoto, T
  - Kimpton, Lawrence A
  - King, Carl D
  - King, Mrs. Coretta
  - King, Cristina P
  - King, George C
  - King, Mrs. Louisa
  - King, Margherita A
  - King, Willard V
  - Kingston, J
  - Kinkead, Margaret
  - Kinsolving, A B
  - Kinstler, Everett Ray
  - Kirk, Grayson
  - Kirk, Rudolf
  - Kirkbride, Franklin B
  - Kirkpatrick, Evron M
  - Kirkpatrick, Ralph
  - Kirkstein, Lincoln
  - Kisburg, Nicholas
  - Kistiakowsky, George B
  - Klabin, Israel
  - Klaus, Samuel
  - Klein, David
  - Klein, Richard A
  - Klensch, Mrs. Patricia
  - Klinger, Wallace
  - Klitgaard, Mrs. Georgina
  - Klonis, Stewart
  - Knachel, Philip A
  - Knapp, Joseph G
  - Klein, Ted
  - Knappen, Marshall
  - Knauth, Felix
  - Knauth, Oswald
  - Knickerbocker Hospital
  - Knight, Clinton
  - Knight, Douglas
  - Knight, M M
  - Knopf, Alfred A
  - Knopf, Mrs. Blanche W
  - Knox, Gordon
  - Knox, Seymour H
  - Koch, Adrienne
  - Koch, John
  - Koch, Richard H
  - Kocher, A Lawrence
  - Kohn, Benjamin
  - Kohn, Hans
  - Kolb-Lena Cheese Company
  - Kone, Eugene
  - Konefsky, Samuel J
  - Koren, William, Jr.
  - Korff, Serge A
  - Kouwenhoven, John F
  - Kramer, Mrs. Dorothy Dunn
  - Kramer, Samuel Noah
  - Krans, Harold
  - Kraus, Edward H
  - Kray, Elizabeth
  - Kreen Akarore Indians
  - Kresky, Edward M
  - Kress, Harrison
  - Kress, Jocelyn
  - Kristeller, Paul Oskar
  - Kristol, Irving
  - Krock, Arthur
  - Kroeber, Alfred L
  - Krould, Harry J
  - Kroupa, Melanie
  - Krout, John Allen
  - Krug, Mark M
  - Kruger, P Gerald